Guide to the Antone's: Home of the Blues Collection
The Wittliff Collections
- Interview and Performance Videos, 2003; 13299
  - Port Arthur driving w/Cliff & Jack, museum part 4, August 19, 2003 (Box 10, Item 147)
  - Port Arthur end of museum interview with Curator part 5 (Box 10, Item 148)
  - Arthur road trip – Jack interview part 6 (Box 10, Item 149)
  - Pete Mayes interview, August 20, 2003 (Box 10, Item 150a)
  - Pete Mayes interview, August 20, 2003 (Box 10, Item 150b)
  - Sandra Bullock interview, August 21, 2003 (Box 10, Item 151a)
  - Sandra Bullock interview, August 21, 2003 (Box 11, Item 151b)
  - Charlotte Finch – Ironworks/ Ilsa Haynes, August 21-22, 2003 (Box 11, Item 152a)
  - Charlotte Finch – Ironworks/ Ilsa Haynes, August 21-22, 2003 (Box 11, Item 152b)
  - Susan Antone interview, August 21, 2003 (Box 11, Item 153a)
  - Susan Antone interview, August 21, 2003 (Box 11, Item 153b)
  - Charlie and Will Sexton interview, August 21, 2003 (Box 11, Item 154a)
  - Charlie and Will Sexton interview, August 21, 2003 (Box 11, Item 154b)
  - Last Clifford interview 1 of 2, August 22, 2003 (Box 11, Item 155a)
  - Last Clifford interview, August 22, 2003 (Box 11, Item 155b)
  - Last Clifford interview 2 of 2, August 22, 2003 (Box 11, Item 156a)
  - Last Clifford interview, August 22, 2003 (Box 11, Item 156b)
  - VHS stuff from the club (Box 11, Item 157)
  - Albert Collins on stage with Clifford and Derek -Big Oaks footage -Buddy Guy with Cotton and Rodgers -Denny Freeman – Blue Monday -Kim Wilson and Stevie Ray Vaughan -KVUE -Albert Collins -Eddie Taylor (Box 11, Item 158)
  - Dough Sahm VHS dub (Box 11, Item 159)
  - Luther Tucker – I got the blues -Sunnyland Slim -Sunnyland Slim solo -Eddie Taylor-Justa Bad Boy -Buddy Guy-Strong Hands -Eddie Taylor-Leann Sit Down (Box 11, Item 162)
  - Doug Sahm from VHS (Box 11, Item 165)
  - Clifford interview re-shoot (Box 11, Item 168a)
  - Clifford interview re-shoot (Box 11, Item 168b)
  - Viewing/archival DVD copies of tapes, 2003 (Box 12, Item 1-168)
  - Interview and performance tape inventories listing dates, DV cam numbers and corresponding VHS numbers, 13312 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Marketing and Publicity, 13313
  This series contains photocopies of reviews of Antone's: Home of the Blues, press releases, biographies, a cast list, a Certificate of Registration, the film trailer, and a Fox 7 News clip about the film's premiere at the 2004 SXSW film festival.
  - Photocopies of reviews of Antone's: Home of the Blues, 13314 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Contents
    Austin Chronicle, March 12, 2004
    Living Blues, July/August 2006
    Big City Blues, Aug. – Sept. 2006
    VideoScope-The Phantom of the Movies, Fall 2006
    Home Media Retailing, April 30 – May 6, 2006
    The Hollywood Reporter, May 24, 2006
    The New York Times, May 25, 2006
    CityBeat Cincinnati, June 16, 2006
    Chicago Sun-Times.com, June 2, 2006
    GuideLive.com, June 16, 2006
    Houston Chronicle, June 13, 2006
    Los Angeles Times, June 16, 2006
    Movie City News, Aug. 1, 2006
    DVD Talk, June 6, 2006
    The Rasputin Manifesto, June 2006
    Billboard.com, June 10, 2006.
  - Press releases from Silverstar Entertainment and Koch Vision, 13315 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Cast list, synopsis, introduction of director, executive producer and producer, and biography sheet for majority of musicians in DVD. One red folder which originally housed press releases and other information.
  - A photocopy of the certificate of registration filed with the Copyright Office for Antone's: Home of the Blues, 13316 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - One DVD of the trailer for Antone's: Home of the Blues, with one archival DVD copy, 13317 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Includes one DVD with the news story of the premiere of Antone's: Home of the Blues at the South by Southwest Film festival; news story aired on Fox 7 News in Austin, Texas, with one archival DVD copy
- Documentary, 13318 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  This series includes a commercial DVD copy of Antone's: Home of the Blues, as well as a VHS tape and DVD viewing copy of the premier version, labeled "1st edit premiered @ SxSW 3/04".